Coalition of Adult Education Organizations (CAEO) Records
Coalition of Adult Education Organizations (CAEO) Records
- Organizations, councils, commissions (alphabetical)
  - American Association of Community and Junior Colleges (AACJC), Committee on International Adult Education, 1980 (Box 13)
  - American Council on Education (ACE), 1980-1984 (Box 13)
  - American Society for Training and Development (ASTD), 1980-1982 (Box 13)
  - Association of University Evening Colleges (AUEC) undated (Box 13)
  - The College Board, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Committee for Education Funding, 1987-1988 (Box 13)
  - Committee for Full Funding of Education Programs, 1972-1974 (Box 13)
  - Council for the Progress of Nontraditional Study/Institute for Educational Development, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Council of Graduate Schools, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Council on the Continuing Education Unit--Conference Report, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Eisenberg Associates, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education, 1973-1975 (Box 13)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education--Rejection, 1973-1974 (Box 13)
  - Independent Sector, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Intergovernmental Advisory Council, 1981-1982 (Box 13)
  - Joint Council on Economic Education, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 13)
  - Kellogg Foundation--Lifelong Learning Leaders Retreat, Nov. 29-Dec. 1, 1982 (Box 13)
  - National Advisory Council on Adult Education (NACAE), 1980 (Box 13)
  - National Advisory Council on Continuing Education, 1982 (Box 13)
  - National Association of Black Adult Educators (NABAE), 1972 (Box 13)
  - National Association for Public Continuing and Adult Education (NAPCAE)--Newsletter, 1978 (Box 13)
  - NAPCAE/NIE Curriculum Development Task Force, 1976 (Box 13)
  - National Center for Educational Brokering, 1976-1977 (Box 13)
  - National Center for Higher Education Management Systems (NCHEMS), 1974-1976 (Box 13)
  - NCHEMS Technical Report #102, 1977 (Box 13)
  - National Council on Community Services for Community and Junior Colleges undated (Box 13)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), 1973 (Box 13)
  - National University Continuing Education Association (NUCEA) undated (Box 13)
  - National University Extension Association (NUEA)--Response to Higher Education Amendments, 197?- (Box 13)
  - NUEA/AEA/ACHE Dissent, 1977 (Box 13)
  - NY State Education Department--Norman Kurland, 1973-1975 (Box 13)
  - NY State Education Department, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Pennsylvania Department of Education--Curriculum Development Project, 1984-1986 (Box 13)
  - Postsecondary Education Convening Authority (PECA), 1976 (Box 13)
  - PECA--Clearwater Conference, 1976 (Box 13)
  - PECA, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Project Literacy U.S. (PLUS), 1986-1988 (Box 13)
  - Syracuse University Resources for Educators of Adults, 1980-1982 (Box 13)
  - United States Association of Evening Students (USAES), 1972-1983 (Box 13)
  - U.S. Department [Office] of Education, 1973 (Box 13)
  - U.S. Department [Office] of Education--Lifelong Learning Project, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - U.S. Department, 1980 (Box 13)
  - U.S. Department of Education, 1981-1982 (Box 14)
  - U.S. Office of the President, 1981-1982 (Box 14)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education (WICHE), 1976 (Box 14)
- International organizations
  - General (alphabetical)
    - ICAE--newsletters, 1970; 1982-? (Box 14)
    - International Council for Adult Education (ICAE)--Proposal, 1972 (Box 14)
    - ICAE, 1972-1976 (Box 14)
    - ICAE--International Adult Education Status Report, 1976 (Box 14)
    - ICAE, 1977-1980 (Box 14)
    - ICAE--Executive Committee, Washington, D.C., 1980 (Box 14)
    - ICAE--Ad Hoc Committee, 1980 (Box 14)
    - ICAE--handouts, 1980 (Box 14)
    - ICAE, 1981 (Box 14)
    - ICAE--International Associates, Applications, 1981-1982 (Box 14)
    - ICAE--Paris Conference, 1982 (Box 14)
    - ICAE, 1982-1986 (Box 14)
    - UNESCO, 1969-1970 (Box 14)
    - UNESCO--IBE meeting on Documentation and Information Services for Adult Education, May 29-June 1, 1973 (Box 14)
    - UNESCO--An Information System in the Specialized Area of Adult Education, 1973 (Box 14)
    - UNESCO, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
    - UNESCO--Adult Education Information Notes, 1975-1981 (Box 14)
    - UNESCO--Draft Recommendations, 1976 (Box 14)
    - UNESCO--Cooperative Educational Abstracting Service (CEAS), 1978 (Box 14)
    - UNESCO, 1982-1986 (Box 14)
    - United Nations Bicentennial, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
    - United Nations University, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
  - Conferences (chron.)
    - Third International Conferences on Adult Education, July 25-Aug. 7, 1972 (Box 14)
    - Multi-National Workshop on Adult Education, Jan. 5-10, 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
    - Seminar on "Structures of Adult Education in Developing Countries, With Special Reference to Africa", 1975 (Box 15)
    - Hemispheric Conference on Adult Education, Ottawa, May 28, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Hemispheric Conference--Norceca, 1976 (Box 15)
    - International Associates--Annual Meeting, National Adult Education Education Conference, Oct. 30, 1981 (Box 15)
- Papers and reports
  - An Analysis of the Statistics Canada Adult Education Survey, 1985 (Box 15)
  - The CAEO: An Historical and Network Analysis--Dissertation, 1985 (Box 15)
  - CAEO Retrospective: The First Ten Years, undated (Box 15)
  - CAEO Through the Years (A. Charters), 1976 (Box 15)
  - CAEO--Year Three, 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - Competencies and Characteristics Required for Literacy, Employability Occupational Success and Effective Citizenship, undated (Box 15)
  - A Framework and Language for Postsecondary Education, 1976 (Box 15)
  - A Nation At Risk, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Papers, Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
  - Presidents Report, 1982(?) (Box 15)
  - A Statement on Coalition of Adult Education Organizations (A. Charters), 1976 (Box 15)
- Miscellaneous
  - Adult Education Opportunity Act of 1971 (Box 16)
  - Chinese Adult Educators--visit, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Dissertation Material--Walter Varner, 1975-1976 (Box 16)
  - International Women's Year, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
  - Laubach--Archive, 1974 (Box 16)
  - Charles Longacre, 1976-1980 (Box 16)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 16)
  - Seminar--Publications in Continuing Education, June 8-10, 1971 (Box 16)
  - State 1202 Commission, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
  - State Advisory Councils on Vocational Education--Directory, 1980 (Box 16)
- Pamphlets, newsletters, flyers
  - Adult and Continuing Education Today (Box 16)
  - Aging (Box 16)
  - Clearinghouses (Box 16)
  - Community Education (Box 16)
  - Lifelong Learning (Box 16)
  - Misc. flyers (Box 16)
  - Misc. newsletters (Box 16)
  - Inventory of Folder Titles as Received by George Arents Library, 1991 (Box 16)